Seidenberg, Jacob Additional Arbitration Files 5635
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files
1971-1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seidenberg, Jacob
5635
10 cubic feet
10 linear ft.
Arbitration decisions, records.
5677189
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 04, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5519: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5217: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Case Files 5808: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5808: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5229: Jacob Seidenberg Additional records 5571: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5666: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5706: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5756: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5773: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5900: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5935: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5988: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5605: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Records 5953: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Records 5194: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Files 5468: Jacob Seidenberg Arbitration files 5032: Jacob Seidenberg Injunction Study 5175: Jacob Seidenberg Taft-Hartley Maritime Dispute Records
Arbitration, Industrial.; Seidenberg, Jacob
5677189
- A-B. (Box 1)
  - Aberdeen Proving Grounds IAMAW Local 2424 FMCS 77K20806, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AAA 1630013273 AP-Local 570-IBT, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Stevedoring Corporation IBT Local 175 FMCS 74K0 2085,2086 Brown et al., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A&P Tea Co.- Local 311- IBT FMCS 78K0 3177, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Awards-Public Law Board 969, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allied Chemical-IBP Local 851-FMCS 76K0 1492, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bokery and Pension Funds OPEIU-FMCS 78K06335, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bell Telephone Pa Fed. Of Telephone Workers AAA 14300575, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Badger-Dowhation-IUMSWA-Local 87-FMCS 75K04534, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bell Telephone co. of Penna. Fed. Of Telephone Workers AAA1430008774, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Public Law Board no. 969-B&O-BLE, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Branch Motor Freight and Local 557, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Baltimore Type & Composition Company-Balt. Typographical Union FMCS 76K 24779, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Braniff v. ALPA, DAL-156-74-F, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bladensburg Unemployment Corp. (CCC), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Ca (Carrier Files). (Box 2)
  - UTU-T Case No. 2272 Carrier File# 44-780 Board Award No. 343, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - UTU Case No. 1319 Carrier File No. 45-188-2 Board Award no. 328, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - UTU-T Case No.1329 Carrier File No. 46-409-45 Board Award No. 329, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - UTU-T Case No.1386 Carrier File No. 45-344-13 Board Award No. 331, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - UTU-T Case No.1388 Carrier File No. 46-841-22 Board Award No. 332, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - UTU-T Case No.1519 Carrier File No. 46-648-1 Board Award No. 334, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - UTU-T Case No.1561 Carrier File No. 45-357-3 Board Award No. 335, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - UTU-T Case No.1640 Carrier File No. 93-738-C-8 Board Award No. 339, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - UTU-T Case No.2720 Carrier File No. 44-789 Board Award No. 383, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - UTU-T Case No.1767 Carrier File No. 45-106-615, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - UTU-T Case No.2541 Carrier File No. 44-788 Board Award No. 344, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - UTU-T Case No.2271 Carrier File No. 44-878 Board Award No. 392, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - UTU-T Case No.1379 Carrier File No. 46-184-A-47 Board Award No. 330, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - UTU-T Case No.1398 Carrier File No. 44-574-3 Board Award No. 333, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - UTU-T Case No.2718 Carrier File No. 44-790 Board Award No. 382, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - UTU-T Case No.1614 Carrier File No. 93-797-40 Board Award No. 313, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - UTU-T Case No.1725 Carrier File No. 46-231-14-1 Board Award No. 374, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - UTU-T Case No.1629 Carrier File No. 48-1060-144 Board Award No. 338, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - UTU-T Case No.1609 Carrier File No. 93-772-2-83 Board Award No. 373, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - UTU-T Case No.1574 Carrier File No. 93-422-A-365 Board Award No. 336, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - UTU-T Case No.1528,1529 StLSW Files nos. PR-84006 Board Award No. 320, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - UTU-T Case No.1399 Carrier File No. 93-678-E-80 Board Award No. 323, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - UTU-T Case No.1534 Carrier File No. PR-87964 Board Award No. 324, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - UTU-T Case No.1525 Carrier File No. 44-769 Board Award No. 319, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Scope and Contents
    Brakeman
  - UTU-T Case No.1505 Carrier File No. 45-413 Board Award No. 313, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - UTU-T Case No.1512 Carrier File No. 45-410 Board Award No. 315, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - UTU-T Case No.1533 Carrier File No. 44-770 Board Award No. 316, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - UTU-T Case No.1530 Carrier File No. 45-411 Board Award No. 317, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - UTU-T Case No.1531 Carrier File No. 45-412 Board Award No. 318, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - UTU-T Case No.1536,1537 Carrier File No. PR-88059 Board Award No. 325, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - UTU-T Case No.1338 Carrier File No. 47-335-471 Board Award No. 332, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - UTU-T Case No.1991 Carrier File No. 93-422-B-662 Board Award No. 380, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - UTU-T Case No.1992 Carrier File No. 45-418 Board Award No. 340, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - UTU-T Case No.2089 Carrier File No. 48-991-34 Board Award No. 381, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - UTU-T Case No.2085 Carrier File No. 45-420 Board Award No. 391, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- C-Ea (Eastern Airlines). (Box 3)
  - Continental Telephone-CWA Grievance, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Crown Cork, Seal Co.-IAM 74K06974 Local 1672, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Clinchfield Railroad Company, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Community Services Ad. AFGE Local, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - CWA-CWA Staff Union- AAA 16014375, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Crown Cork Seal-IAM FMCS 75K018490, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Communication Workers of America and OPEIU - Local 2 AAA 163014276, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Board Of Education Charles County and Education Association of Charles County, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Board of Education Charles County and Charles County AAA, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Defence Logistics Agency APGE 2047 FMCS 78K02825, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - DC Government-IBPO-IAFF, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Eastern Air Lines-AMAW 9BA-45-78, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Eastern Air Lines-IAM SBA Case #2-77 Grievance, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Eastern Air Lines-IAM SBA 20-77 Grievance-MIA, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Eastern Air Lines- AMAW Case#367-76 Grievance PHL, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Eastern Air Lines-IAM SBA 62-74 63-74, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Eastern Air Lines-ALPA-32474, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Eastern Air Lines-ALPA No. 129/74, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Eastern Air Lines-IAM SBA #474-74, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Eastern Air Lines-ALPA 64-74, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - VFR 373 393, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Ea-Lo (Eastern Airlines-Long Island Railroad). (Box 4)
  - Eastern Airlines Board Of Adjustment, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Air Lines-ALPA No. 14-77 C Schick, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Air Lines-IAM 29-74 36-74, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - E.I. DuPont Company Ampthill Rayon Workers 77K15636, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Ford Fair Stores Inc.-Warehouse Employees Union- Local 570, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - FMCS 76K04059 Potomac Electric-Electric Utilities Employees Union, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - FOP-Sheriff Department 75-1G-R-23, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Grant Ford, Inc. Teamster Local 922 FMCS 76K01905, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Board Of Education-Hartford County, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Public Law Board 2051150 BLE, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Public Law Board No. 1500-ICG-UTU, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 32- PBA 560, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Kleen-Rite Corp.- SEIU-Local 82 FMCS76K06313, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Koppers Co.-IAM-FMCSK012096, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Library of Congress 77K19832, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Lo-No (Long Island Railroad). (Box 5)
  - Mass Transit Ad. Amalgamated Transit Union Div. 1300, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Mutual Broadcasting Co AFTRA Wash-Balt Local AAA 163013877, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - McClean Timeking Co.- Local 557, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Montgomery County Education Association. 16390115-74, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Public Law Board no.618 Monongahela - UTU, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Maloney Concrete-Local 639 IBT FMCS Case 78K06991, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Montgomery County Education Association MCEA- AAA39017276, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Board of Education of Montgomery County and Montgomery County Council Supporting Serviced Employees AAA 16390015 76, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NLRB-NLRB Union, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- No.-P. (Box 6)
  - Public Law Board No. 1256 Norfolk Western- UTU, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Public Law Board No. 1477- BRAC, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Public Law Board 42159-NW-UTU, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Public Law Board No. 1611 N.W.R.R.- BRAC, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Prince Willian County School Board and Prince William County Education Association-AAA 1639 178-76, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - County Public Schools- AFSCME-Local 2250 Grievance, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Penn Brass and Copper Company IUE Local 615 AAA 55-30-0113-76, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Prince George's County School Board and Prince George's County Educaiton Association (Grievances), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Prince George's County PERB Police Civilian Association AFSCME 75-P6-R-21, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - PRINAIR-BRAC, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Award no. 9 Public Law Board no.669, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Public Law Board Meeting Award no. 10, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Prince Willian County School Board and Prince William County Education Association-AAA 1639001579, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Penn Central Merger- BRAC, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- P-S. (Box 7)
  - Philadelphia Federation of Teachers-School District of Philadelphia. 1439005476 MIA Back Pay Adjustments, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Exhibit Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Prince George's County Public Schools PGCEA Warner Grievance, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Public Law Board 2035J Submission of Dispute, 1968-1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    1968-1976
  - Prince George's County Public Schools PGCED (Wehrle Grievance), 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Prince George's County PERB- 75-PGR-24 AFSCME-Central Services, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Preston Trucking Co. Local 557, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Roper Eastern Corporation -UFW AAA 14301434755, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac Railroad Co., 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    June 1967
  - Public Law Board No. 1648 SP-BLE, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - SBA #849 NW-UTU, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Sheller-Gerbe Corp. IUOE- Local 387 FMCS 76KD8771, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- S-V. (Box 8)
  - Sinai Hospital of Baltimore and Dulnet 1199E, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - G.B.M.C., Lutheran, Provident, Exhibits H-34-H41, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - John Sexton and Co. Local 639 AAA 1630 0109 76, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Toledo Lakefront Doc. ILA-Local 158, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Chemicals Inc. USWA Local 12180 FMCS 78 K0 2413 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Lime Company- USWA Local 14948- FMCS 76K010367, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- W. (Box 9)
  - West-IGC RR CICC Judicial Exhibit No. 28101, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Wahmann Manufacturing USWA L690 AAA 1430 0790 76-S, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Washington County School Board and Education Association of Washington County, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - WestVaco - UPIU FMCS K00143, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Union Contracts (1936-1973). (Box 10)
  - Railroad Unions Handbooks (folder 1 of 3), 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Pay, Regulations, Agreements
  - Railroad Unions Handbooks (folder 2 of 3), 1972-1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Railroad Unions Handbooks (folder 3 of 3), 1972-1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Paper Mill Workers Unions, 1971-1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Rates of Pay, Agreements, Regulations
  - Education, Teachers Associations, 1971-1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Agreements, Rates of Pay, Regulations
  - Industrial and Steelworkers Unions, 1971-1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Pay, Agreements, Regulations